Guide to the Stephen Rodefer Papers, 1955-1994
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES III: MANUSCRIPTS BY OTHERS
  - Subseries: General
    - Pearlman, William poems (TMs with ALS, TLS) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Perelman, Robert "The Story of My Life" (TMs with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Peterson, Tom poems 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Petrol, Robert poems (TMs reprint with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Reed, Pat "An Hour of Silence in Mud Slide" (TMsS with TL) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Robertson, Kell poems (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Rodefer, Penny "Boetian Thebes..." (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Rodefer, Penny (Kaplan) "Similarities" (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sale, Arthur "The long and the short of it is ?" (TMs with ANS) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Seown, Mark poems (TMsS amd TMs reprint with AN) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Serban, Ioan 4 plays (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Sidel, Frank "Everything I Got" (AMsS) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Tiso, Philip "Drinkin' the Hemlock" (TMs with AL) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Tysh, Chris "In the Name" (TMsS with AMS) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Tysh, Chris: PD/1-PD/II (TMs reprint with TLS) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Walsh, Charles poems (TMsS and TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Ward, Geoff "The First Elegy" (TMs with AN by S. Rodefer) (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Wesling, Donald review of Redo (TMs with TLS) (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Wetmore, Bill "Stephen Rodefer: Dialect and Dialectic" (TMs reprint with AN by S. Rodefer and ANS by BW) (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Wieness, John "To Chet Baker" (AMs) (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Young, Geoff poems (TMs, TMs reprint with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Young, Geoff: "High Angle Shots" (TMs reprint with AN, TLS) (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Young, Geoff: "Sensibility" (TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Ziolkowski, Thad poems (TMs with TLS, AN) (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - [Antoin?] "Opening Day" (AMsS) (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Jul [?] poems (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - [?] "From Orchestra or a Poem of Dauncing," "Calypso's Island" (TMs and AMs) (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Subseries: Fervent Valley Manuscripts
    - Unidentified (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Brenner, Summer poems (TMs with AN by S. Rodefer) (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Bukowski, Charles "Six" (TMs with TLS) (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Creeley, Robert "Flesh" (TMs in TLS) (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Creighton, Jane "Directions" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Duquet, Richard (Fall 72" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Franks, David (TMs reprint and TMs with TL) (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Gierach, John (TMs with TL) (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Ginsberg, Allen "2 am Dirty Jersey Blues" (TMsS with AN) (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Hirschman, Jack poems (TMs with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Jones, Joan Simon poems (TMs with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Levitt, Peter "Lingam on your Collar" (TMsS) (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Lifshin, Lyn "Oh Yes" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Light, Frederick Lazarus "New York Sonnet" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Malanga, Gerald poems (TMsS) (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Ortiz, Simon "My Grandfather: Antonio" (TMsS reprint) (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Potts, Charles "Dear Eddy" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Rotkin, Jeanne S. poem (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Siotis, Dino "My Greece" (TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Smith, Phil "pisghetti" (TMs reprint, signed) (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Snyder, Richard poems (TMsS) (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Vermont, Charlie poems (TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Vermont, Charlie and Anne poem and cartoons (TMs and AMs reprint with ALS) (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Waldman, Anne "Notorious" (TMsS with AN) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Whalen, Philip (AMsS and TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Young, Geoffrey "Partial Suicide Brings Spaghetti" (TMs) (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Subseries: Poets Theater Manuscripts
    - Corder, Eileen "Busy Wrong" (TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Corder, Eileen "Mister Sister" (TMs with SR notes) (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Harrymon, Carla "Third Man" (TMs with SR notes) (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Perelman, Robert "The Alps" (rehearsal TMs with SR notes) (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Robinson, Kit "Collateral" (TMs with SR notes, TMs reprint) (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Tzara, Tristan "The Gas Heart" (rehearsal xerox) (Box 19, Folder 61)
- SERIES IV: TEACHING/ UNIVERSITY MATERIALS
  - Subseries: Archive For New Poetry
    - acquisition information: general correspondence (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - acquisition information: Lyn Hejinian Papers (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - acquisition information: Steve McCaffery Papers (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - acquisition information: Carl Rakosi Papers (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - acquisition information: Aram Saroyan Papers (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - acquisition information: Ron Silliman Papers (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - acquisition information: Jack Spicer Papers (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - acquisition information: Sulfur (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - acquisition information: John Taggart Papers (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - acquisition information:: United Artists archive (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - correspondence: internal (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - correspondence: perfomance review (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - correspondence: research, information inquiries (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - correspondence: Taggart/Howe/Oppen controversy (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - documents: Associate Curator's position (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - correspondence: job status, personal leave, etc. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - correspondence: University policies and review protocol (2) (Box 20, Folder 17-18)
    - from folder marked "From D. Wesling": newsletter materials (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Oppen conference materials (1986) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Oppen support materials: photocopies (2) (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Oppen: Of Being Numerous (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Oppen: The Uncollected Published Poems (photocopy) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Reading Series and Newsletter materials (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Subseries: Teaching Materials
    - SUNY Albany: Bibliography, Poetry holdings, c.1963-66 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - SUNY Albany: handouts from Creeley class, 1966-67 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Albany: handouts from Olson course, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - SUNYAB materials 1963-67 (3) (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
    - U. of New Mexico 1969: English Dept. Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - U. of New Mexico: English Dept. information, profiles (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - U. of New Mexico: Love/Lust controversy Investigation Committee (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - U. of New Mexico: Love/Lust controversy: printed matter (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - U. of New Mexico: Reading Series correspondence (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - U. of New Mexico: Reading Series materials (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - U. of New Mexico: tenure correspondence (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - 1983 talk: "Influence" correspondence (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - 1983 talk: "Influence": drafts n.d. (4) (Box 22, Folder 3-6)
    - 1983 talk: "Influence": draft n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 1983 talk: "Influence": Jan. 1, 1983 (TMs reprint) (2) (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - U.C.S.D. 1985-6 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - U.C.S.D: Summer, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cambridge Seminar, Jesus College, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - England: Reading Correspondence 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - England: materials 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - S.F.S.U. Spring 1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Berkeley Fall 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - CCAC Fall 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Cambridge/Wilson Fellowship Fall 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - coursepacks for art/poetry seminars (Box 23, Folder 3-7)
- SERIES V: RODEFER MANUSCRIPTS
  - Subseries: Amherst
    - Akenside's Complacent "Hymn" and Blake's "Mad Song," n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - A Conversation 1959 (TMs with Prof. Gould's AN) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - on Donne n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - on Dryden n.d.(AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Duality and Synthesis: Albrecht Duress n.d. (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - from envelope: Stranger Early Material 56-8 (As) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Exam bluebooks: English 425 and 64 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Exercise on Johnson's Review (Mass) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - The Greatness of Tolstoy...n.d. (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - on James Joyce (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Keats and Shelley: Fear and Soul n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Richard II as a Historical Document n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Unity and Disunity in Sonnets by Bowles and Coleridge n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Wordsworth the Evangelist n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Fragments n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Subseries: Graduate School
    - The American and Its Preface n.d. (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Chaucer's "Troilus and Criseyde" n.d. (AMs) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - From Darkness to Light: A Case for Hawthorne's Position... May 19, 1965 (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Did Donne Know Shakespeare? n.d. (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - English Renaissance Poetry n.d. (AMs) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Hawthorne n.d. (AMs) (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Note for a Hawthorne Paper Mar. 11. 1965 (TMsS with AN) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Olsen Notes Sept. [1965] (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - On the Problem of Order in Shakespeare's Sonnets n.d. (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - The Poetical Works of Christopher Pitt Jan. 6, 1963 (AMsS) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - The Recoil of Despair: Narrator and Ending in Chaucer's "Troilus" n.d. (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Resolution and Ambiguity in Hawthorne's Tales Apr. 9, 1965 (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Shakespeare and the Sonnet Jan. 15, 1965 (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - on Sir Gawain n.d. (AMs) (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - The Symbolic Middle of the Narrative Mask: Where is Moby Dick? Apr. 23, 1965 (TMs) (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - on Victorian Poets n.d. (AMs) (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Subseries: Ph.D. Materials
    - A Form of Women: an Essay in the Content of Robert Creeley's Poems Feb., 1966 (TMsS with AN) (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: William Carlos Williams and Creeley (photocopies) (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Creeley and Corman Mss. from Indiana University (photocopies) (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Creeley materials from Olin Library, Washington University (photocopies) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Ph.D proposal; bibliography (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Ph.D proposal; drafts (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Ph.D proposal; typescript Jan. 5, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Transcribed Robert Creeley poems (5) (Box 25, Folder 5-9)
    - "A & C: An Idyl in One Act" Mar. 9, 1982 (rehearsal TMs reprint) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - "A & C: An Idyl in One Act" Mar. 9, 1982 draft-Nov. 20, 1993 performance program (TMs with AN) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - "Andy Hit with Iodine" Jun., 1980 (TMs) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - "Artist's Life" n.d. (TMs reprint, signed) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - from The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: n.d. (3) (Box 25, Folder 14-16)
    - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: galleys (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: production material (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: typescript (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - "Brief to Butterick" (TMsS with AN) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - "Carrousel sur la Place Rouge" May 11, 1989 (AMsS reprint with ALS) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Chalcedony: unfinished series Oct. 16, 1984 (TMsS with AN) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Child of Faust" Jan. or Nov., 1990 (TMsS reprint with AN) (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - collaboration: with Steve Benson, Intersection for the Arts (TMsS with AN) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - collaboration: with George Butterick and Fred Wah: "3 Free Poems" 1966 (TMs reprint) (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - collaboration: with Ben Friedlander c. Feb. 20, 1984 (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - collaboration: with Jessica Grim and others Nov. 11, 1984 (AMs) (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - collaboration: with Pat Reed (AMs) (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - collaboration: wih Pat Reed (TMs and AMs reprint) (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Downbeat essay (under Gene Callous) c. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Emergency Measures: n.d. mixed drafts (2) (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Emergency Measures:: correspondence (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Measures:: draft (TMs with AN) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Measures:: galleys and corrections (3) (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
    - "Fidel is not the Hero of Castro Street" n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - film script fragment for film made at Buffalo, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - "Found: a Modern Masterpiece," intro. to Carl Rakosi's early poems c. 1993 (TMs reprint with ALS) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Four Lectures: "When one day at last..." computer variables of opening line n.d. (TMs) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Four Lectures:: front matter, index (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Four Lectures: miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Four Lectures: original notes, drafts; "Sleeping with the Light On" n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Four Lectures: paste-up and production (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Four Lectures: "Plane Debris": drafts (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Four Lectures "Plastic Sutures": drafts (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Four Lectures "Plastic Sutures": proofs with AN (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Four Lectures pretext/coda (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Four Lectures "Words in Works in Russian": drafts (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Four Lectures n.d. early typescripts (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Four Lectures final amended typescript (bound) (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
    - Four Lectures final typescript (1981; bound) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - fragment n.d. (AMs) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - "Frottage" May 5, 1992 (AMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - "Hangem All Smoking Fireball" May 5, 1992 (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - "Imitation W" n.d. (AMs) (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - "The Inexplicable History of Music" n.d. (AMs) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - In the American Tree: galleys (TMs reprint) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Jello Biafra essay for Search and Destroy #9 (TMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - The Knife n.d. (TMsS) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - The Knife: drafts 1965 (TMs, AMs) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - The Knife: final typescript n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - The Knife: mock-up n.d. (AMs) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - "Last New Hampshire Poem" Jun. 9, 1992 (AMsS reprint) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Life Feast, partial typescript 1969 (TMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Lives of the Artists: title/cover page n.d. (AMs reprint) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Lives of the Artists: fragments n.d. (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Lives of the Artists: n.d. (TMs) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Lives of the Artists: n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Lives of the Artists: n.d. II (TMs with AN) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Lives of the Artists: Mss with supplements n.d. (TMs reprint) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Lives of the Artists: original sequence; many poems later omitted (TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Lives of the Artists: working Ms n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Lives of the Artists: miscellany Oct. 16, 1980 (AMs, TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Lives of the Artists: full draft Oct. 16, 1980 (TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Lives of the Artists: fragments May 29, 1981 (AMs, TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Lives of the Artists: from folder "Mss pulled from Lives..." Sept., 1988 (TMs with AN) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Lives of the Artists: final Ts (TMs reprint) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Lives of the Artists: folder with notes (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Lucy Melos Dec. 25, 1994 (AMs postcard, with drawing) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Moncanard, "Mangez du pain" (TMs reprint, inscribed handmade cover) Jan. 1, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - "News from the Far Side of the Common Pond: Andrew Crozier's Regular Bead..." Jan. 22-Mar. 20, 1985 (TMs with AN, TLS reprint) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Nomad Life: original typescript (TMS with AN) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Nomad Life:: (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Nomad Life:: (TMs reprint) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - note by Rodefer as Jean Calais for KPFA radio May 1, 1978 (TMs reprint) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - "Old Times Now" corrected galleys Sept., 1991 (TMS reprint with ANS) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - "Once upon a Smile" n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - from One or Two Love Poems from the White World n.d. (AMs, TMs) (2) (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - from One or Two Love Poems from the White World: galleys and cover (TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - from One or Two Love Poems from the White World: paste-up (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
    - Oriflamme Day: paste-up (3) (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
    - Oriflamme Day: photocopies of paste-up (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - "Painted Poetry": proofs (AMs) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Passing Duration: first typescript of Ms, then titled "Among the Atomic Events" n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Passing Duration: second Ts of "Among the Atomic Events" (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Passing Duration: n.d. envelope with notes (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Passing Duration: n.d. mixed poems (AMs, TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Passing Duration: n.d. typescripts (TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Passing Duration: 1986 sections: rejected (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Passing Duration: dated 2/85 (bound; TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Passing Duration: final text dated 5/89 (bound; TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - "Questions for Snyder" Oct. 15, 1985 (TMs with AN) (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Safety: n.d. (TMs with AN) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Safety: n.d. bound typescript (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Safety: "MIAM" #1 1977 (TMs with AN) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Safety: "MIAM" with notes (TMs with AN) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Safety: paste-up (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Safety: photocopied paste-up (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - "so and so now" Jun. 9, 1992 (TMs with ALS & AN reprint) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Spec Trek IV UCSD Library Christmas skit 1986 (AMs,TMs reprint) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - "Spleen Amongst the Swans of the Queen" n.d. [under pseudonym Anthony Lake] (TMs with ANS reprint) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - "Spurwhang Filch" (TMs reprint with ANS) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - "Stiller Blemish" n.d. (TMs reprint with AN) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Undone Business: Charles Olson 80th Birthday Celebration [With Levi-Straus and Thackeray] (TMs with AN) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Villon: galleys (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Villon: paste-up (3) (Box 30, Folder 14-16)
    - Earliest poems--Amherst College 1959-61 (AMs, TMs) (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mss from Buffalo 1960-1970 (6) (Box 30, Folder 18-23)
    - Mss from Buffalo 1960-1970 (2) (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
    - Mss from Buffalo, Newspapers from series 1960-1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - miscellaneous 1960-1970 (5) (Box 31, Folder 4-8)
    - untitled MS--poems 1961-76, many unpublished (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - unpublished MS--overlaps with Life Feast, 1969 (2) (Box 31, Folder 10-11)
    - miscellaneous c. 1970-1987, mostly unpublished (4) (Box 31, Folder 12-15)
    - Ms given to George Mattingly for Blue Wind Press, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - material from Black Mountain Conference, 1987(AMs) (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - mixed folder, from envelope "What Jean returned" 1989 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - poems sent to Andrea Hollowell; MacDowell Colony, Nov.5-Dec. 7, 1989 (AMs reprint) (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - unidentified: poems (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - untitled play, 2/92 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Subseries: Reviews And Journalism
    - catalogue: Joe Brainard exhibit, UCSD 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - essay: The Library of Label," for Contrast II, Spring 1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - interview: on 1965 Berkeley Poetry Conference, Poetry Flash, June, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - from folder marked "journalism"--Wet, downbeat reprints (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - "Priory": publicity broadsheet with Rodefer's poem for Stockbridge reading, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - publicity materials for Four Lectures: 1982 Poetry Center Book Award (TMs with AN and AMs lists) (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: American Book Review v.6, 1988 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Booklist on Villon, Oct. 15, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Gerald Burns on Villon and Lectures, 1983 (unpublished TMs reprint) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Library Journal on Four Lectures, Dec. 15, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Poetics Journal #3, 1983 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: The Poetry Project Newsletter #98 (original; 1983) (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: San Francisco Chronicle, Oct. 19, 1983 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: San Francisco Review of Books, May 1978 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Sulfur #8, 1983 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - reviews of Rodefer's work: Times Literary Supplement, Dec. 9, 1983 (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 16)
- SERIES VI: SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS
  - address books, 1959-1992 (Box o.s. box 32 B)
  - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: cloth cover (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: jacket and jacket mock-up, The Bell Clerk's Tears Keep Flowing: spine stamp (metal; in o.s. box A); Joe Brainard exhibition catalogue: layout (o.s. box A); McDowell poem, on cardboard box (o.s.) (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Oriflamme Day photocopies (oversize) with envelope notes (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Parentheses Writing Series 1987: pamphlet with Rodefer poem, "Numberless Shadows" (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Passing Duration: Rodefer's paste-up of cover atop inscribed book, Mentalite Detail (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - The Poems of Francois Villon: Rodefer's annotated edition of the Galway Kinnell translation (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - removed from correspondence: Michael Glossen to Rodefer, Lovecraft's The Doom that Came to Sarnath (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - removed from correspondence: cassette tape, Yattabaoth Hose Off (Box 32, Folder 24)
- SERIES VII: PHOTOS
  - Subseries: Removed From Correspondence
    - from Jaime Arrangoiz, Feb. 10, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - from Arnold Bomner, June 9, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Meghan Boucher, Mar. 28, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - from Kathryn Brown, May 3, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Margery Cantor, 1975-6 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - from Victor Coleman, Nov. 13, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - from Ben Friedlander, 1991-3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Andrea Hollowell, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - from Cathleen Hoolihan Burke, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - from Laura Kasischke, May 11, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - from Jean Lowe, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - from Jesse Rodefer, May 17 [1976] (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Penny Rodefer (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - from Allen Schiller, Jun. 1, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - from Geoff Young [c. 1980] (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Subseries: Loose Or Unlabeled Photos
    - Rodefer family, 1947 or 1948 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - 1970s: photos of Rodefer (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - 1970s Rodefer with family (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - 1970s: Rodefer with others (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - 1970 photo: Kandel Love/Lust photo (with reprint) (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - 1980s: misc. photos (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - 1980: from "Andy Hit with Iodine," Wet 1980 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - undated: photos of Rodefer (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - undated: photos with family, others (Box 33, Folder 24)
- SERIES VIII: AUDIO-VISUAL MATERIALS
  - Subseries: Video Materials
    - Home movies shot by Rodefer's father; "Baseball", c. 1940 and "Yellowstone", 1942 (16 MM) (Box 34)